In this video, we're gonna talk about the core data structure used in compilers, the
在本视频中，我们将讨论编译器中使用的核心数据结构
abstract syntax tree. To briefly review, a parser traces the derivation of a sequence
抽象语法树。简单回顾一下，解析器跟踪序列的派生
of tokens but this by itself Is not all that useful to the compiler because the
，但这本身对编译器并不是很有用，因为
rest of the compiler needs some representation of the program. It needs an
睡觉的编译器需要一些程序的表示形式。它需要一个
actual data structure that tells it what the operations are in the program and how
实际的数据结构，告诉它程序中有哪些操作以及如何操作
they're put together. Well, we know one such data structure is called a Parse Tree
它们是放在一起的。我们知道一种这样的数据结构叫做解析树
but it turns out that a Parse Tree really isn't what we wanted to work on. Instead,
但事实证明，解析树并不是我们想要做的。相反，
we wanted to work on something called an Abstract Syntax Tree. And the Abstract
我们想做一种叫做抽象语法树的东西。和“抽象”
Syntax Tree is really just the Parse Tree but with some details ignored. We have
语法树实际上只是解析树，但是忽略了一些细节。我们有
abstracted a way From some of the details of the Parse Tree. And here's an
从解析树的一些细节中抽象出一种方法。这是一个
abbreviation that you'll see, ASTs stand for Abstract Syntax Tree. So, let's look
您将看到的缩写，ASTS代表抽象语法树。那么，我们来看看
at the grammar. Here's the grammar for plus expressions over the integers and we
在语法方面。下面是整数上加号表达式的语法，我们
also parenthesize expressions. And here's a string and after lexical analysis, what
也可以用括号括起表达式。这是一个字符串，在词法分析之后，
do we have? Well, we've got a sequence of tokens again with their associated lexemes
我们有吗？好的，我们又得到了一系列的记号和它们的相关词位
telling us what the actual strings were. And that gets past into the parser and
告诉我们实际的弦是什么。然后进入解析器，然后
then we build a parse tree. And here's a parse tree for that expression. Now, if
然后我们构建一棵解析树。这是该表达式的解析树。现在，如果
it's expressed that this representation, the parse tree is actually perfectly
可以说，这种表示形式，解析树实际上是完美的
adequate for compilation. We could do our compiler using the parse tree. This is a
足以汇编的。我们可以使用解析树进行编译器。这是一个
faithful representation of the program. The problem is that it would be quite
忠实地代表节目。问题是，这将是相当
inconvenient to do that and to see this, it only point out some features of the
这样做和看到这一点都不方便，它只指出了
parse tree. First of all you can see if the parse tree is quite robust so for
解析树。首先，您可以看到解析树是否相当健壮，因此对于
example we have here a node e and it has only one child. So when there's only one
例如，我们这里有一个节点e，它只有一个子节点。所以当只有一个
successor of the, of the node, what is that really doing for us? Well, we don't
节点的后继者，这对我们到底有什么作用？嗯，我们没有
really need the e at all, we could just put the, The five right here and, and make
真的很需要e，我们可以把这个，五个放在这里，然后
the tree smaller and similarly for the other single successor nodes. Furthermore
该树更小，并且对于其他单个后继节点类似。此外，
these parentheses h ere, well these are very important in parsing because they
这些圆括号在这里，嗯，这些在解析中非常重要，因为它们
show the association of, of this, of the arguments with respect to these two plus
显示与这两个加号有关的论点的关联性
operations. It shows that this plus is nested; this plus down here is nested
运营部。它显示这个加号是嵌套的；下面的这个加号是嵌套的
inside. Of this plus up here But once we've done the parsing, the tree structure
在里面。再加上这里，但是一旦我们完成了解析，树结构
shows us the same thing. We don't need to know that these were inside a parenthesis,
向我们展示了同样的东西。我们不需要知道这些是在括号里，
that the fact that these two expressions or the argument of this plus already tells
这两个表达式或者这个加号的论点已经告诉我们
us all we need to know. And so, you know? All of these nodes in here are also in a
我们都是我们需要知道的。所以，你知道吗？这里的所有这些节点也都在
sense redundant. We don't really need that information anymore. And so we prefer to
感觉是多余的。我们真的不再需要这些信息了。所以我们更愿意
do is to use something called an Abstract Syntax Tree that just compresses out all
所做的就是使用一种称为抽象语法树的东西，它只是压缩了所有
the junk in the Parse Tree. So here is a. Abstract syntax tree or a hypothetical
解析树里的垃圾。所以这里有一个.抽象语法树或一个假设的
abstract syntax tree that would represent the same thing as the parse tree on the
抽象语法树，它与
previous slide and you can see here we've really just cut it down to the essential
上一张幻灯片，您可以在这里看到，我们已经将其简化到最重要的部分
items. We have the two+ nodes. We have the three. Arguments and the association is
物品。我们有两个+节点。我们有三个人。参数和关联是
just shown by which plus node is nested inside the other. We don't have any of the
刚才显示了哪个加号节点嵌套在另一个加号节点中。我们没有任何
extraneous nonterminals. We don't have the parenthesis. Everything is much simpler
无关紧要的非终端。我们没有括号。一切都简单多了
and you can imagine that it'll be easier to write algorithms that walk over a
您可以想象，编写遍历
structure like this rather than the, the rather, elaborate structure we had on the
像这样的结构，而不是我们在
previous slide. Of course again is called an abstract syntax tree because it
上一张幻灯片。当然，我们也将其称为抽象语法树，因为它
abstracts away from the concrete syntax. We suppress details of the concrete syntax
从具体语法中抽象出来。我们隐藏了具体语法的细节
and just keep enough information to be able to faithfully represent the program
只要保留足够的信息就能忠实地代表节目
and compile it.
然后编译它。